HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE General President's Files on Microfilm
1982-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/008 mf
21.89 cubic feet
197 microfilm reels
Records, microfilm.
6273222
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), was a United States labor union representing workers of the hospitality industry, formed in 1891. In 2004, HERE merged with the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE) to form UNITE HERE. HERE and later UNITE HERE were affiliated with the AFL-CIO until September 2005, when the General Executive Board of UNITE HERE voted in to leave the AFL-CIO and join with the Change to Win Coalition.
Scope and Contents
Negative copies of GP Local Corresp. - Reel 1-9, 11-13, available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hotels--Employees--Labor unions--United States; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions--United States; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union; Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant, and Tavern Employees' Union
6273222
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #1 Trusteeship, #5 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 1)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #6 Merger Paper, #10 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 2)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #11 G.P. Correspond., #34 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 3)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #35 G.P. Correspond., #75 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 4)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #76 G.P. Correspond., #217 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 5)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #226 G.P. Correspond., #353 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 6)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #355 G.P. Correspond., #886 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 7)
- 1982-83 G.P. Local Correspondence -- #631 G.P. Correspond., #886 G.P. Correspond. (Reel 8)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #1, Local #7 (Reel 9)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #7, Local #12 (Reel 10)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #17, Local #31 (Reel 11)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #34, Local #54 (Reel 12)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #54, Local #75 (Reel 13)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #76, Local #118 (Reel 14)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #121, Local #226 (Reel 15)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #226, Local #332 (Reel 16)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #336, Local #527 (Reel 17)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #531, Local #631 (Reel 18)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #634, Local #878 (Reel 19)
- 1984 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #879, Local #886 (Reel 20)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #1, Local #8 (Reel 21)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #8, Local #24 (Reel 22)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #25, Local #46 (Reel 23)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #47, Local 86 (Reel 24)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #86, Local #217 (Reel 25)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #217, Local #436 (Reel 26)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #450, Local #767 (Reel 27)
- 1985 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #767, Local #886 (Reel 28)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #1, Local #9 (Reel 29)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #9, Local #16 (Reel 30)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #17, Local #25 (Reel 31)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #26, Local #31 (Reel 32)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #34, Local #40 (Reel 33)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #40, Local #40 (Reel 34)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #40, Local #40 (Reel 35)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #40, Local #54 (Reel 36)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #54, Local #84 (Reel 37)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #86, Local #88 (Reel 38)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #88, Local #200 (Reel 39)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #206, Local #309 (Reel 40)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #310, Local #623 (Reel 41)
- 1986 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #628, Local #886 (Reel 42)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #1, Chicago, IL, Local #12, Cinti, OH (Reel 43)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #14, Denver, CO, Local #29, Lawrence (Reel 44)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #30, San Diego, Local #74, St. Louis (Reel 45)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #75, Toronto, Local #217, New Haven (Reel 46)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #220, Eureka, CA, Local #450, Forest Pk. (Reel 47)
- 1987 G.P. Local Correspondence -- Local #457, Butte, Mt., Local #886, Birmingham (Reel 48)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #1, Chicago, IL, Local #21, Rochester, MN (Reel 49)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #24, Detroit, MI, Local #56, Billings, MT (Reel 50)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #57, Pittsburgh, PA, Local #206, Winnipeg, Canada (Reel 51)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #215, Wausau, WI, Local #483, Monterey, CA (Reel 52)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #495, Washington, D.C., Local #5, Honolulu, HI (Reel 53)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #6, New York, NY, Local #21, Rochester, MN (Reel 54)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #24, Detroit, MI, Local #47, Edmonton Calgary (Reel 55)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #49, Sacramento, CA, Local #246, Oklahoma City (Reel 56)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #251, Houston, TX, Local #767, Regina Saskatchewan (Reel 57)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1986-1989 -- Local #775, Nashville, TN, Local #886, Birmingham, AL (Reel 58)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #1, Local #11 (Reel 59)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #11, Local #17 (Reel 60)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #17, Local #36 (Reel 61)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #40, Local #150 (Reel 62)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #150, Local #301 (Reel 63)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #309, Local #498 (Reel 64)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #531, Local #767 (Reel 65)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1990 -- Local #767, Local #886 (Reel 66)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #1, Chicago, IL, Local #19, Trusteeship App. (Reel 67)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #19, San Jose, Calif., Local #19, Trusteeship App. (Reel 68)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #19, Trusteeship App., Local #31, Montreal, Quebec (Reel 69)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #32, Washington, DC, Local #226, Las Vegas, NV (Reel 70)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #100 New York, NY, Local #226, Las Vegas, NV (Reel 71)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #226 Las Vegas, NV, Local #457, Butte, Montana (Reel 72)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #466, Rochester, NY, Local #634, Phila, Penn. (Reel 73)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #636 Prince Rupert, Local #886, Birmingham, AL (Reel 74)
- G.P. Local Correspondence 1991 -- Local #2, Palewicz, CS, Local #11, '89 Elect. (Reel 75)
- G.P. Local Legal - Local #21 Minn. MN Bldg, Local #803 Ft. Riley (Reel 76)
- G.P. Local Legal - Local #847, St. Jude, Local #34 Agency Fees (Reel 77)
- G.P. Local Legal - Local #40, Hotra Case, Local #40, 1988 Elect. (Reel 78)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 1-1992, Local 6 (Reel 79)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 7-1992, Local 37-1992 (Reel 80)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 40-1992, Local 165-1992 (Reel 81)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 166-1992, Local 471-1992 (Reel 82)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 471-cont'd., Local 19-1993 (Reel 83)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 20-1993, Local 215-1993 (Reel 84)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 217-1993, Local 590-1993 (Reel 85)
- G.P. Local Corres., Local 604-1993, Local 879-1993 (Reel 86)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, "A" 1982-1983, Todays Issues '80-'83 (Reel 87)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, "C" 1982-1983, Ed. Programs - Local Union Officers (Reel 88)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, Ed. Programs '82-'83, "H" 1980-1983 (Reel 89)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, A.S. Hansen '80-'83, I.F.E.B.P. '82-'83 (Reel 90)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, I.F.E.B.P. Seminars, Minimum Dues '74-'75 (Reel 91)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, "N" 1982-1983, A. Phillip Randolph (Reel 92)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, RTW Defense foundation, A.S. Weiss Assoc., Inc. (Reel 93)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1983, Wolfgang Memorial Race (Reel 94)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1986, "A", CIE (Reel 95)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1986 - City of Hope, Massachusetts Mutual (Reel 96)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1986 -Wm. Meyers - Jan.-Feb., 1985 (Reel 97)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1986 - Wm. Meyers-Misc. File, Fred W. Rondon 86-1 (Reel 98)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence, 1986 - St. Jude's Children's Res., A.S. Weiss (Reel 99)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Alaska Reports, Attorney Bills Misc. (Reel 100)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - "B" Misc. Files, Day w/the all AM (Reel 101)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - "E" Misc. Files, A.S. Hansen (Reel 102)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Health Care Cost Con. L.C.C.R. (Reel 103)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence -L.C.L.A.A., William L. Meyers (Reel 104)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - William L. Meyers, Organizing Pro-Per. (Reel 105)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - O.S.H.A. Operation Push (Reel 106)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - "R" Misc. Files, Sky Chefs Misc. (Reel 107)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Solidarity Day, Robert Juliano Files (Reel 108)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Robert Juliano Misc., T.I.P. Reporting (Reel 109)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - T.I.P. Reporting, I.U. & Regional (Reel 110)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - I.U. Cars & Vans, Western Office (Reel 111)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Western Office, AFL-CIO Dept. (Reel 112)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - AFL-CIO Education, AFL-CIO-Public Emp. (Reel 113)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - AFL-CIO-Public Emp., AFL-CIO-ILCA (Reel 114)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - AFL-CIO-IUD, AFL-CIO-Maritime Tra. (Reel 115)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - AFL-CIO-Geo. Meany Cnt., AFL-CIO-Solidarity (Reel 116)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - AFL-CIO-State Bodies, Congress Railroad (Reel 117)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Conrail-U.S. Railway Assoc. (Reel 118)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - CIE 1978-80, Corcoran School Bldg. (Reel 119)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Corcoran School Bldg., Food & Beverage Trades (Reel 120)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Fast 1983-1984, Fast-House Afire (Reel 121)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Misc. A 1986-87, Misc. B (Reel 122)
- G.P. Misc. Correspondence - Misc. C, Misc. J (Reel 123)
- G.P. Misc. - Misc. K, M. Segal 7/12/87 (Reel 124)
- G.P. Misc. - Sky Chef, Misc. W. (Reel 125)
- G.P. Misc. - '88 Amer. Against Gov., '88 Boy Scouts (Reel 126)
- G.P. Misc. - Misc. C 1988, '88 Inquiries (Reel 127)
- G.P. Misc. - '88 Invititations, OSHA 1988 (Reel 128)
- G.P. Misc. - Misc. P 1988, Sky Chef 1988 (Reel 129)
- G.P. Misc. - Misc. T 1988, '87-88 Dept. Educ. (Reel 130)
- G.P. Misc. - Dept. Int'l. Affairs Housing investment (Reel 131)
- G.P. Misc. - AFL-CIO '87 IUD, '87-88 Metal Trades (Reel 132)
- G.P. Misc. - AFL-CIO '87 Misc., AFL-CIO Regional Conf. (Reel 133)
- G.P. Misc. - Dept. of Research, AFL-CIO '85-88 Fast (Reel 134)
- G.P. Misc. - Fast Lie Detectors, Fast Smoking (Reel 135)
- G.P. Misc. - R.J. Immagration Political Monies (Reel 136)
- G.P. Misc. - Political Monies '88, Wm. L. Meyers '87 (Reel 137)
- G.P. Misc. - Wm. L. Meyers '87 (Reel 138)
- G.P. Misc. - Wm. L. Meyers '88, Pension-Investments (Reel 139)
- G.P. Misc. - Pension-Investment, NCCMP- 1985-1986 (Reel 140)
- G.P. Misc. - NCCMP- 1986-88, Public Relations (Reel 141)
- G.P. Misc. - Public Relations '81, Communication World (Reel 142)
- G.P. Misc. - Un. Privilege Benefit, UPBP Mem. Request (Reel 143)
- G.P. Misc. - Letters to Bk. Of NY, RLEA 1987 (Reel 144)
- G.P. Misc. - RLEA 1988, Spec. Assessments (Reel 145)
- G.P. Misc. - Spec. Assessments, Fraternal Greetings (Reel 146)
- G.P. Misc. - Fed. Consultants, '86-87 OSHA (Reel 147)
- G.P. Misc. - Pension Fiduciary, John Krolick Arb. (Reel 148)
- G.P. Misc. - Arb. #86-28 Roberts Pres. Comm. Crime (Reel 149)
- G.P. Misc. - Hearing Transcripts, CIE Reprint (Reel 150)
- G.P. Misc. - Assorted Material (Reel 151)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, Alum. Brick & Glass, Int'l. Police Assoc. (Reel 152)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, AM. Postal Workers, Attorney - Jan.-Mar. (Reel 153)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, Attorney - Apr.-Jun., Donations Jan-Jun (Reel 154)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, Donations Jul-Dec, IUF 1989 (Reel 155)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, JAL-NIKKO, Resumes-Employment (Reel 156)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1989, A. Phillip Randolph-A.S. Weis Assoc. (Reel 157)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 401K-1990, Attorneys 1990 (Reel 158)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 Attorneys 1990, Gray Davis 1989 (Reel 159)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 Donations 1990, Invitations 1990 (Reel 160)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 IUF 1990, OSHA 1990 (Reel 161)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 "P" 1990, Pension Welfare 1990 (Reel 162)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 Pension Welfare Contract, Resume's 1990 (Reel 163)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 "S" 1990, Robt. Juliane 1989 (Reel 164)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 Robt. Juliane 1989, RLEA 1990 (Reel 165)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 RLEA 1990, RLEA 1989 (Reel 166)
- G.P. Misc. - 1990 RLEA 1989 (Reel 167)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Misc. A, Styles, Paul L. (Reel 168)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Meyer, Suozzi, English, Linens of the week (Reel 169)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Liquor Dept. of Labor (Reel 170)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Dept. of Justice Invitations (Reel 171)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Invitations-Cont'd -- A. Philip Randolph (Reel 172)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Welfare & Pension Misc. T (Reel 173)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1991-Thank You - A.S. Weiss, Assoc. (Reel 174)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Misc. ABC's 1992, Tomar, Simonoff, Adourian (Reel 175)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Teed, Teed & McPhee 1992, IU Financial Reports 1992 (Reel 176)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Fraternal greetings, 1992, Invitations, 1992 (Reel 177)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Ireland Trips, 1992, Welfare & Pension 1992, Pt. 4 (Reel 178)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Welfare & Pension 1992, Pt. 5, Davis, Cowell & Bowe, Pt. 1 (Reel 179)
- G.P. Misc. - Correspondence 1992-1993 - Davis, Cowell & Bowe, Carson's Int'l. 1991-93 (Reel 180)
- GP Misc. Corres. 1992-93 - Xmas Party 1993, "I", 1993 (Reel 181)
- GP Misc. Corres. 1992-93 - (Reel 182)
- GP Misc. Corres. 1992-93 - "J" 1993, Feder & Assoc. Wel/Pen '93 (Reel 183)
- GP Misc. Corres. 1992-93 - Welfare Pension, 1993, A.S. Weiss Assoc., 1993 (Reel 184)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 1 (Reel 185)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 2 (Reel 186)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 3 (Reel 187)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 4 (Reel 188)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 5 (Reel 189)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 6 (Reel 190)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 7 (Reel 191)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 8 (Reel 192)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 9 (Reel 193)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 10 (Reel 194)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 11 (Reel 195)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 12 (Reel 196)
- GP Local Corresp. - Reel 13 (Reel 197)